# Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva



🔘 batlkhagva.e@gmail.com 🕡 dave-bat.vercel.app 🕻 @enkhdavaa 🛅 Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva

I have five years of experience in software development. In this period, I gained in-depth knowledge in scrum/agile, software design, digital twin, and model based testing. Moreover, I consistently improves my technical skills in the area of web and game development, and machine learning.

## **Experience**

## Software Designer

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Present

**Q** Eindhoven, NL

- · Created an infrastructure strategy for using Model-Based-Testing at Thermo Fisher Scientific.
- Created state transition models for testing various subsystems of the TEM microscope at Thermo Fisher Scientific.
- Designed and developed 3D virtual hardware simulator for testing the control software of a factory at ICT Group.

.NET C#, Unity 3D, C++

## **Software Designer Trainee**

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

**Q** Eindhoven, NL

• Designed and developed a proof of concept for 3D virtual hardware simulator tool. The tool is for testing software using Unity3D game engine.

.NET C#, Unity 3D, Matlab

### **Embedded Software Engineer**

Tavan Bogd Management

Mar 2018 — Sep 2018

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

- Contributed to implementing contactlesss payment using wireless technologies (Bluetooth and WIFI).
- · Created a windows desktop application for exchanged data with Oracle DB.

.NET C#, C

#### **Embedded Software Intern**

Innovation for High Performance Microelectronics LLC

**□** Jan 2017 — Mar 2017

• Frankfurt (Oder), DE

• Implemented firmware drivers for a platform that measures a power consumption with high precision.

 $\mathbf{C}$ 

## **Embedded Software Engineer**

Ametros Solutions LLC

☐ Jul 2015 — Sep 2016

• Ulaanbaatar, MNG

- Developed firmware drivers for home automation devices (light-switch, intrusion and air quality sensors).
- · Contributed developing wireless data transmission between devices.

.NET C#, C

## **Projects**

### **Model Based Testing (MBT)**

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Oct 2021 — Present

Eindhoven, NL

- · Developed state transition models for random test generation
- Created a testing workflow for development process
- · Developed adapters for CI by connecting SUT with MBT
- Created documentations and presentations for users

Axini, .NET C#, C++, GIT, Jenkins, Shell scripting

# Center Of Excellence (COE)

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Oct 2022

Eindhoven, NL

- Designed and developed a virtual 3D factory simulator to replace hardware testing dependency
- Developed HAL interface for the simulator (DT) for higher abstraction layer software
- Created CI & CD for the simulator (DT)

Unity3D, OPC-UA, .NET C#, GIT, Docker, Bamboo CI

## Virtual Hardware Simulator for Transmission Electron Microscope (EngD)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

Eindhoven, NL

• Deisgned and implemented a 3D virtual hardware simulator for firmware and software testing so that testing is not dependent on real hardware.

Unity3D, .NET C#, GIT, Matlab, Docker

# **Dependency Management and Scope Control for** HMI products (EngD)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Sep 2019 — Dec 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Codeveloped a domain-specific language and a livecode dependency checker to detect software architechture

**Role:** Software engineer co-developing a live dependency checker

Roslyn, .NET C#

For more projects next page ...

### **Education**

# **Engineering Doctorate (EngD) in Software Technology**

Eindhoven University of Technology

☐ Oct 2018 — Oct 2020

**Q** Eindhoven, NL

### **BSc Electronics Engineering Technology**

Mongolian University Of Science and Technology

☐ Aug 2011 — Jul 2015

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

## **Skills**

C#
Agile Scrum
Git
C++
JavaScript and TypeScript
Python

## **Hobby**

- Bouldering, Improvization, Running
- Playing guitar, sketching
- Game development

## **Projects**

# Designing Smart Landing System for Agricultural Drones (EngD)

AgroTech

☐ May 2019 — Jul 2019

P Eindhoven, NL

**Goal:** Design and implement the drone control software to save time of field analytics

**Role:** CI engineer and software engineer, responsible for proposing design choices and co-developing the drone control

## Python, DroneKit

### Face AI for Condition Monitoring (EngD)

Philips Healthcare

**□** Jan 2019 — Apr 2019

Eindhoven, NL

**Goal:** Add new features to the existing remote consultation system using AI services (Microsoft face AI, Amazon Rekognition)

**Role:** Software developer/Configuration manager responsible for co-developing back-end services using C# and implementing a CI pipeline

Microsoft Face AI, Amazon rekognition, .NET C#